你不知道上周发生了什么
You don't know what happened last week?
我可没空告诉你
Well, I don't have time to tell you.
我忙着呢
I'm busy.
等你老爸出狱后
What's your dad gonna do when he gets out of jail
我告诉他你每天都忙着跟人搞基
and I tell him you spend all day with orange boy
你觉得他会怎么做
rubbing your dicks together?
明天给我五百块  不然我就打给他
$500 tomorrow, or I call him.
今天我孩子出生
The day my babies are born,
你居然把收银台里的钱都掳走了
You steal cash from the register?
收银台是你的  钱是我的
Yeah, your register, my cash.
把你口袋里的钱给我
Empty your fucking pockets.
他死定了
He's a fucking dead man.
你们好啊
Well, hello.
我和罗杰·奔跑·树分手了
Roger Running Tree and I broke up.
但是孩子们  弗兰克
But the children, Frank.
我和罗杰本来都要结婚然后收养他们了
Roger and I--we were gonna get married and adopt them
结果他露出了真面目
before he showed his true colors.
我只需要一纸婚书
All I need is a marriage certificate.
弗兰克  你愿意娶我吗
Frank, will you marry me?
在此  我宣布  你们成为合法夫妻
It is my honor to declare you man and wife.
你可以亲吻新郎了
You may kiss the groom.
他情况危急
He's in serious condition,
所以我们把他挪到名单第一位了
so they moved him up the waiting list.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
-他要得到一个新肝了  -什么
- He's getting a liver. - What?
家长会的时候  你要装成我男朋友
Need you to meet my mom and dad for parents' weekend.
去见我父母
Pretend we're together.
就收拾收拾吃个晚餐
Just clean up for a dinner?
不  不要收拾
No, no cleanup.
我得好好吓吓他们
I need to scare the living shit out of them.
那是你的兄弟姐妹吗
Those your brothers and sisters?
这里是四个  车上还有三个
Four of them, three more in the van.
我家住这里
My family lives in there.
住超市里吗
In the supermarket?
不是  住在货车里面
No, in the van.
马修
Hey, Matthew.
什么是她有而我没有的
What does she have that I don't?
喂
Hello?
你不知道你惹上谁了  贱人
You don't know who you messed with, skank.
我才不在乎
I don't give a shit if you're ten years old
你是不是还在玩布娃娃的十岁毛孩
and playing with dolls.
你想开战  现在我们开战了
You want a war, you got it.
菲奥娜没有回家
Fiona never came home.
她违反了假释条例
She violated probation.
嗨  利普  对不起
Hi, Lip. I'm sorry.
我真是一团糟
I fucked up.
你周旋于各种琐事
You're juggling so many things,
我还不断出岔子
and I am just fucking up.
我现在真的需要帮助
I need some help now.
你先自己说吧
So you want to go first?
无耻家庭
第四季第十一集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  扎克不渣      重案组李Sir      落      君君
■
翻译：  姚小事     爱卿遛小鸟     猛回头     Greentie
时间轴：  信徒       浓子       大喷子
■
校对：  Greentie      落
后期： 孤帆          总监： 落
■
我们这是要去哪儿
Where are we going?
看起来像是要去迪凯特惩教署
Looks like Decatur Correctional.
有多远
How far away is that?
三个小时左右的车程吧
Three hours or so.
什么
What?
但愿你上过厕所了
Hope you peed.
你因为什么事被抓的
What'd they nab you for?
为什么在这辆巴士上  这可不是去观光旅游
Why you on this bus? It ain't a sightseeing tour.
我
I, uh...
我违反了假释条例
I broke probation.
我捅了我男友老婆肚子一刀
I stabbed my boyfriend's wife in the stomach a little bit.
那婊子说她有孕在身
Bitch claimed she was pregnant.
我知道她向来满嘴胡话
Knew she was full of shit
这么说无非是想缠着他不放
and was saying it to hold on to him.
我得证明她撒了谎不是
Had to prove her wrong, right?
结果原来她说的是真的
Turns out she wasn't lying.
我去
Oops.
老爸
Hey, pops.
感觉如何
How you feeling?
你今天看起来好多了
You are looking better today.
跟你的外公问好  恰奇
Say hi to your grandpa, Chuckie.
-他能听到我们说的话吗  -当然
- Can he hear us? - Of course he can.
这是能让他醒过来的唯一办法了
That's the only way he's gonna wake up.
告诉他我们的感受
When we tell him how we feel,
那些话会渗入他的潜意识里
it seeps into his subconscious,
并且刺激到他的大脑
it tickles his brain,
然后很快他就能醒过来了  明白吗
and it'll make him open his eyes soon, okay?
-快点  -好吧
- Come on. - Okay.
外公
Hi, grandpa.
妈妈说等你醒了之后咱们就去露比餐厅大吃一顿
Mama says we can go to ruby Tuesday's when you wake up.
早上好
Good morning.
我叫艾米丽
I'm Emily.
我需要一颗新的心脏
I need a new heart.
我深表遗憾
Oh, I'm so sorry.
你自己的心脏出什么问题了
What's wrong with yours?
别这么没礼貌
Hey, don't be rude.
老天
Oh, my god.
别整天"老天老天"的挂在嘴上  先生
Don't you "Oh, my god" Me, mister.
这是我的儿子  恰奇
This is my son, Chuckie.
我叫萨米
I'm Sammi.
我叫温蒂  是她妈妈
I'm Wendy, her mom.
她  她得了心肌病
She, uh... She has cardiomyopathy.
我的心肌无法供应足量的血
My heart muscle doesn't pump enough blood
给我身体的其他部分
into the rest of my body.
所以你才像个吸血鬼吗
Is that why you look like a vampire?
查尔斯·奈文斯·斯洛特  赶紧给我闭嘴
Hey, Charles Nevins Slott, you stop that right now.
快道歉
Apologize.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
We are so sorry.
-老天  -没关系
- Oh, god. - It's okay.
不要紧
It's okay.
加拉格先生是你爸爸吗
Is mr. Gallagher your father?
没错
Sure is.
我没有爸爸
I don't have a father.
-艾米丽  -我生病后他就走了
- Emily. - He left when I got sick.
妈妈说他无法面对  所以只好一走了之
Mama says that men can't handle tragedy, so they leave.
不是谁都想听我们家的丑事  艾米丽
Not everybody needs to hear our dirty laundry, Emily.
不用顾忌我们
No, don't worry about us.
在芝加哥这里没人比我们家的丑事更多了
We have the dirtiest laundry in chicago.
加拉格先生也在等心脏吗
Is mr. Gallagher waiting for a heart too?
他之前一直在等肝脏
He was waiting for a liver,
几天前刚做了移植手术
and then he had a transplant the other day,
现在他快痊愈了
and now he is getting all better.
真是个振奋人心的消息啊
That's fantastic news.
听见没  艾米丽  咱们来对地方了
See, Emily? We're in the right place.
米奇是你男友吗
Mickey your boyfriend?
我们是在约会
We hang out.
他在你的床上
He's in your bed.
是啊  他的家人简直是一场噩梦
Yeah, his family is a nightmare.
我想我交到女友了
Think I got a girlfriend.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是的  她的家人也是一场噩梦
Yeah, her family's a nightmare too.
谁不是呢
Whose isn't?
你爱米奇吗
You love Mickey?
我喜欢他身上的味道
I like how he smells.
你问这么傻逼的问题干什么
What you asking stupid fucking questions for?
你睡觉的时候更友好
You were nicer when you were asleep.
肝移植后弗兰克活了下来
Frank survived his liver transplant,
如果你想知道话
in case you were wondering.
不  不想知道
Nope. Wasn't.
我得去教堂参加洗礼
I got to go over to the church for the christening today.
我以为你不在乎
Thought you didn't care.
-我不在乎  -那你为什么要去
- I don't. - Why are you going, then?
那可是我儿子啊
It's my son, man.
好吧  我换衣服
All right, I'll get dressed.
不不  没关系
No, no, look, it's fine.
我自己去就行
I'll head over by myself.
我几个小时后回来
I'll be back in a couple hours.
什么  你不想让我去
What, you don't want me to go?
可能你不去比较好  猛男
Probably best if you don't, tough guy.
是啊  我不去你当然高兴了
Yeah, for you, maybe.
你为什么找我麻烦
Why you busting my balls, man?
就是好奇我们到底是不是情侣
Just wondering if we're a couple or not.
当然是了
Of course we are.
地下情
A couple that hides?
目前为止进展不错
Hey, it's working out so far, so good.
我有点厌倦了
Getting kind of sick of it.
要命了
Jesus christ, man.
你能不能先让我处理完那件破事儿
How about you let me go deal with that stupid shit
然后再处理你的破事儿
before I deal with your stupid shit?
工作怎么样  亲爱的
How was work, dear?
我有了对称的伤口
I got, uh, matching war wounds.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
查你的分数
Looking up your quarter grades.
他们还没有公布呢
They haven't posted yet.
很好  我不想知道
All right, good. I don't want to know.
我现在压力太大了
I'm too stressed to deal right now.
我看你平均分要拿到B
The way I see it, you need a "B" Average
才能继续拿奖学金
to keep your scholarship.
这个我也不想谈
And I don't want to talk about it either.
我打赌你宏观经济学和哲学会拿到B
I bet you'll get a "B" in macro and philosophy
热力学跟英语会拿到A
and an "A" In thermo and English.
我怎么做你才会闭嘴
What do I have to do to get you to shut up?
如果有东西堵住我嘴巴的话
Well, maybe if I had something else to occupy my mouth.
这个主意好多了
That's a much better idea.
好吧
All right.
-等等  先别  -怎么了
- Wait. Don't. - Why?
让比赛公平一点
Levels the playing field.
我跪下  你就得戴着发网
I'm on my knees. You're wearing a hairnet.
你真是个怪胎
You're a freak.
彼此彼此
Takes one to know one.
对了  我今晚没办法
Oh, hey, look, um, I'm not gonna be able
跟你父母吃饭  好吗
to have dinner with your parents tonight, okay?
我们可以一边说话
No, you could keep doing what you were doing
一边来  操
while we're talki-- - Ow, fuck!
你为什么去不了
Why won't you be able to go, hmm?
你说你能去  你必须去
You said you would go. You're--you're going.
不行  我必须得回家
No, look, I-I got to-- I got to go home.
我得要想办法
I got to figure shit out,
在菲奥娜尊监狱的90天
see how we're gonna pay the bills
我们要怎么养活自己
for the next 90 days while Fiona's in prison.
我们说好的
We made a deal.
是的  那是在我姐进监狱之前
Yeah, that was before my sister went on a bender.
你保证你会帮忙吓我父母
You promised to help terrorize my parents
报答我给了你那么多东西
in exchange for me giving you stuff.
好的  明天吃午饭怎么样
Okay, then how about we get lunch tomorrow?
不行  他们明早要回迈阿密
No, they're leaving for Miami in the morning.
说话要算话
A-a deal's a deal.
你显然没听我说话
You're obviously not hearing me.
你显然也不是一个说话算话的人
And you're obviously not a man of your word.
我可以去勾引乔治老师
I would totally hook up with Mr. George.
他很性感
He's foxy.
但是他结婚了
But he's married.
还那么老
And old.
这只是我们的性幻想老师的名单
This is just our fantasy teacher list.
不一定非要真的发生
It doesn't mean it's gonna happen.
这味道让我要吐了
Ugh, that smell is gonna make me gag.
我们必须要做这个破生物实验吗
Do we really have to do this stupid biology lab?
那是亨利·麦考纳利
There's Henry Mcnally.
他让人很"感性趣"
He's so bang-tastic.
我想要给他口交一下
I want to suck him like a slushee.
他让我内心的雄狮饥渴地咆哮
He makes my loins roar with hunger.
黛比  你好吗
Hey, Debbie, how's it going?
-我  -她
- Me? - Her?
如果你愿意我可以帮你做这个实验
Yeah, I can help you with your lab if you want.
-你知道我的名字  -是啊
- You know my name? - Yeah.
猴子跟她的姐姐说
The monkey said to his sister,
"我不想从那个男人那里买香蕉"
"I don't want to buy bananas from that man."
有人在吗
Knock, knock.
有客人
Visitors.
早上好
Good morning.
希拉
Hey, Sheila.
-看看谁来了  -天呐
- Look who's here. - Oh, my God.
我带好东西来了
I got some special treats.
-太棒了  -一个爱心包裹
- Very nice. - A little care package.
病人怎么样
How's the patient?
他还没醒呢
Well, he still hasn't woken up yet.
弗兰克
Frank.
Frankie.
弗兰克  弗兰克  弗兰克
Frankie, Frankie, Frankie,
弗兰克  弗兰克  弗兰克  弗兰克
Frank-a, Frank, Frank, Frankie.
弗兰克
Frank?
Frank.
弗兰克  你在哪呢
Frank, where are you?
弗兰克  是我  希拉
Frank, it's me, Sheila.
快回来  快回来  不管你在哪里
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
你必须醒过来
You have got to wake up.
你还有丈夫的
You see, you have some husbandly duties
责任要尽
to attend to.
你不能上去
You can't be up there.
你会把他输液的管弄出来
You're gonna knock out his I.V. tubes out.
-下来  -不  我不下来
- Come on. - No, I'm not.
医生跟护士已经尽全力了
The nurses and doctors are doing everything they can,
你只需要让他休息一下就好
and you just need to let him rest.
你知道吗  他休息够了
You know what? He's been resting.
好了  你能下来吗
Okay, so can you get down?
我是在把他叫醒
I'm trying to get him up, for God sakes.
这些即将都是他的孩子了
Listen, these are his soon-to-be children,
我是他妻子
and I'm his wife.
放轻松  小姐
So just take a breather, missy.
是不是啊
Isn't that right, guys?
是的
Right-o.
我们可以跳一段原住民的部落舞蹈
We could do a native American Indian tribal dance
来叫醒他  希拉妈妈
to wake him, mama Sheila.
那是什么
What's that?
我们在学校的文化历史课上学的
We learned about it in our cultural history class at school.
我希望我也能上学
I wish I could go to school.
注意礼貌  艾米丽
Mind your manners, Emily.
抱歉  她不是故意要偷听的
I-I'm so sorry. She didn't mean to eavesdrop.
在这里很难不听到
It's just--it's hard not to in this place.
没关系
Of course.
我叫温蒂
Hi, I'm--I'm Wendy.
这是我女儿  艾米丽
This is my daughter, Emily.
我叫希拉
I'm--I'm Sheila.
我是弗兰克的老婆
I'm--I'm Frank's wife.
这些是他的孩子们
And--and these are his children.
我跟他们可没关系
I'm not related to them.
要不你们来跳一下你们的部落舞吧
Well, anyway, why don't you show us your tribal dance?
听起来不错  不是吗
That sounds wonderful, doesn't it?
又或者
Or we could just let him rest,
我们就让他好好休息
like he's supposed to.
我觉得跳舞这主意不错
I think the dance is a wonderful idea.
我觉得也是
So do I.
我们去买冰冻酸奶
We're gonna go get frozen yogurt.
好的
Okay. All right.
知道怎么去吗
You know where to go?
老爸来了吗
Dad in there yet?
罗尼叔叔去接他了
Uncle Ronnie went to get him.
应该就快到了
Should be here any minute.
这横幅也太烂了
That thing looks like shit.
用太多次了
Been used a lot.
这是特里吗
Is that Terry?
不是
No.
这是我的混蛋老公
It's my piece-of-shit husband.
怎么还没开始
This hasn't even started yet?
-你迟到了  -这不是来了吗
- You're late. - All right, well, I'm here now.
赶紧开始吧
Let's get this show on the road, all right?
我们得等你爸来了再开始
No, we must wait until your father gets here.
相信我  他根本不在乎这个
He doesn't give a shit about the ceremony, trust me.
等下的派对他肯定会出现
He'll be here for the after-party.
他在乎  亲口告诉我的
No, he gives shit. He tells me.
你跟他说过话
You talked to him?
每天都说  我们关系可好了
Almost every day. We've become very close.
真恶心
God, that is so sick.
你又打算跟他上床了吗
Are you gonna start banging him again too?
抱歉  我们必须开始了
Uh, I'm sorry, but we have to start.
45分钟之后我还有个葬礼要参加
I have a funeral in 45 minutes.
-太好了  赶紧吧  -不行  必须等
- Good, yes, fine. Let's go. - No, we must wait.
洗礼必须全家人参加
Whole family needs to be here to witness baptism.
不然呢  就不算数吗
Or what, it didn't really happen?
瞧  还好我们没开始吧
Oh, see? It's good we wait.
-他来干嘛  -我他妈怎么知道
- What is he doing here? - How the hell should I know?
我们赶紧开始吧  行吗
We're--let's get this on the road, all right?
是不是要把孩子扔水里
Aren't you supposed to dunk the kid
还是什么的
in the bowl of water or something?
他说得对
He's right.
我必须开始了
I must start.
好吧
Fine.
主啊  你用圣水给予我们洗礼的启示
Father, you made a sign in the waters for baptism
要终恶扬善
to end sin and begin goodness.
通过洗礼  用水以及你圣洁的灵魂
Through this baptism, Yevgeny is cleansed from sin
洗去伊夫耶尼亚的罪恶  让他重获新生
to a new birth to innocence by water and the holy spirit.
你姐真酷  居然去了迪凯特惩教署
That's so cool your sister's at Decatur.
可能吧
Yeah, I guess.
这些还不够吗
Don't you think we have enough stuff already?
不够  我有七个弟弟妹妹呢
No. I have seven siblings.
得多拿一点
I need something for all of them.
再往这边倒一点
Tip it a little more.
太棒了
Fire in the hole.
我得去医院看我爸了
I'm gonna go visit my father in the hospital now.
-你想一起来吗  -不行
- You want to come? - Can't.
得回货车上了  有个孩子得了支气管炎
Got to head back to the van. One of the kids has bronchitis.
-我得回去看看他  -你应该搬来跟我住
- I need to go check on him. - You should come live with me.
我不能离开他们
I can't leave the other kids.
他们可以一起来
They can come live with us too.
好啊
Okay.
卡尔
Carl.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
把它的皮钉在这里
So pin his skin to the felt.
好样的
Good job.
我看不下去了
Ew, I can't look.
-真有意思  -就是啊
- This is fun. - Isn't it?
说到有意思
Speaking of fun...
我父母这周末不回家
My parents aren't gonna be home this weekend.
你应该过来  我们一起看A片
You should come over, and we can watch porn.
我刚下了好看的
I downloaded sperms of endearment.
我对A片没什么兴趣
I'm not really into porn.
我也是
Me either.
很恶心  是不是
Yeah, it's gross, right?
A片就全是什么"好爽啊"
You know, they're like, "Oh, yeah."
-"干我"  -"好爽"
- "Oh, give it to me." - "Oh, yeah."
"就是这样"
"Just like that."
看这个
Hey, um, look at this.
这是它的肺
Here's his lungs.
酷
Cool.
这是脾脏
And here's his spleen.
还有...
And...
心脏
This is his heart.
送给我
For me?
饶了我吧
Give me a fucking break.
排成一队下车
Off the bus, single line.
别说话  别挤
No talking, no pushing.
快走
Keep the line moving.
如果一副牌里有四个A
If there are four aces in a deck of cards,
那么你从一副牌里抽到A的几率
then the probability of your pulling an ace
就是52分之4
Is 4 over 52...
或者说是13分之1
Or 1/13.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
没有
Nope.
站这儿别动
Stay right there.
你想折磨你父母
You want to torture your parents?
那今晚带他们来我家吃饭
Bring them to my house for dinner tonight.
这是地址
Here's the address.
帮我传过去
Pass that?
我们今晚吃我从食堂
We're having, uh, leftover lasagna
偷来的意面
I stole from the cafeteria.
我能继续了吗
May I continue?
别再说我说话不算话
Don't ever say I'm not a man of my word again.
如果我们不把A放回去
If we don't return our ace to the deck,
那么拿到第二张A的几率...
then the probability of choosing a second ace...
右脚不动  左脚抬起来  停
Jump on your right foot. Pause.
然后换边  停
Now on your left foot. Pause.
膝盖抬高
High knees.
膝盖抬高  有意思
High knees. Interesting.
我不知道这些东西对老爸
I'm not sure all this woo-woo spiritual stuff
能有什么帮助
Is gonna help dad.
你要这么想那肯定没帮助
Not with that attitude, it won't.
我玩的挺开心
I'm having a great time.
你们干嘛呢
What the hell are you guys doing?
我们在试着唤醒弗兰克的灵魂
We're waking Frank's spirit.
这样不就行了
Why don't you just do this?
这是怎么回事
What happened?
他醒了
He's awake!
你成功了  卡尔
You did it, Carl.
我不确定那个是最佳办法
I'm not sure that was the best method.
爸爸  你还好吗
Dad, are you okay?
我这是在哪儿  黛比
Where am I, Debbie?
黛比
Debbie?
我  我是萨咪
It--I'm Sammi.
你在医院里
You're at the hospital.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
我最好去叫医生
I better get the doctor.
妈妈是要去哪儿  利普
Where's mama going, Lip?
老兄  你这是怎么了  我是卡尔
Dude, what's wrong with you? I'm Carl.
或许我该再往他的蛋蛋上来一拳
Maybe I should hit him in the nuts again--
不  不  不  不要啊
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
他醒了
He's awake!
就跟我之前跟你说的那样
Just like I told you.
这是好消息
This is good news.
比预计得快多了
A lot sooner than expected.
他把我们都认错了
He thinks we're different people.
你把他的脑袋弄残了
You screwed his brain on backwards.
弗兰克  你知道你这是在哪儿吗
Frank, do you know where you are?
你现在在圣迈克尔医院的重症监护室
You're in the intensive care unit at St. Michael hospital.
几天前  你接受了一次肝移植手术
You underwent surgery a few days ago for your liver.
妈妈  他在说什么呢
Mama, what's he talking about?
看吧  我就跟你说
See? What'd I tell you?
为什么他会把我们认错呢
Why does he think we're different people?
我们去外面的走廊上谈吧
Uh, let's go out in the hall and talk.
好吧  我们马上就回来  稍等一下
Okay, we'll be right back. Hold on.
加拉格先生出现了术后谵妄的症状
Mr. Gallagher is suffering from postoperative delirium.
好吧  那是什么玩意儿
Okay, what's that?
该情况常见于接受了大型手术的病人身上
It often happens when a patient undergoes intense surgery
因为他们被注射了大量的镇静剂
where a heavy dose of sedation was used.
那  那是永久性的吗
Oh. Is it--is it permanent?
不
Uh, no.
那在术后病人中是很常见的
It's very common in post-op patients.
他会对时间和人物关系产生迷惑
He'll be confused about time and relationships.
当他处于这种精神状态下
All you can do is be patient
你们只能耐心等待
While he's in this altered state,
不用多久  他就会恢复原状的
But he'll be back to his old self soon.
该死
Oh, shoot.
我刚刚动了一下  是不是坏事了
I just moved. Is that bad?
那最糟糕了  现在我把你画成男人了
It's the worst. Now I'm drawing a man.
黛比到底有什么是我没有的
What the hell does Debbie have that I don't have?
她的处女膜
Her hymen.
但你看看她
But look at her.
他已经读11年级了
He's an 11th grader.
她是红头发
She's a redhead.
我喜欢红头发的
I love redheads.
幸亏我昨晚没染头发
Good thing I didn't dye my hair last night.
我现在想吻你  是不是很糟糕
Is it bad that I want to kiss you right now?
就在这儿吗
Uh, right here?
我们会被老师抓的
I think we'll get in trouble.
那去哪儿
Where, then?
我不知道
I don't know.
不如在篮球训练过后
How about after basketball practice,
躲到体育馆地下的楼梯后面吧
Behind the stairs in the gym basement?
好吧
Okay.
很好
Cool.
准备好看我的大作了吗
Ready to see?
是的
Yeah.
不  我只是在开玩笑而已
No, I'm just joking.
真的画得很棒
It's really good.
谢谢
Thanks.
我很高兴你喜欢
I'm glad you like it.
我喜欢
I do.
我非常喜欢
I like it a lot.
我来帮你弄吧
Ah, let me get that for you.
这么多卷心菜够了吗
Is that enough cabbage for you?
我可以自己弄的  没关系的
I can make my own plate. It's fine.
不  一点都不麻烦
No, no problem at all.
来些咸牛肉怎么样
How about some corned beef?
你干嘛这么逢迎献媚的
Why you being such a suck-up, huh?
我俩可是有过节的呢
You and me got a thing we got to settle.
听着  我只是想把一切抛之脑后  明白吗
Look, I'm just trying to put everything in the past, okay?
我现在是个拒服兵役者
I'm a conscientious objector now.
-那他妈是什么意思  -我也不太清楚
- What the fuck does that mean? - I don't really know.
反正跟穆罕默德·阿里有关
Something to do with Muhammad Ali.
和平与爱
Peace and love?
好的  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
太好了  谢谢
Great. Thank you.
叫你男朋友滚蛋
Tell your boyfriend to leave.
你他妈在说什么呢
What the fuck are you talking about?
那个红发男
Howdy doody.
叫他滚蛋  不然我走
Tell him to leave, or I will.
好吧  好吧
All right, fine.
听着  斯瓦特娜要你走人
Look, Svetlana wants you to go.
你想让我走吗
You want me to go?
不  我不想让你走
No, I don't want you to go.
但如果你走的话  事情能简单一些
But the whole thing's gonna go a lot easier if you do.
对你来说或许是吧  但对我呢
for you, maybe. What about me?
这里真的是你想待的地方吗
This really where you want to spend your day off?
你在这儿
You're here.
给我几个钟头
Give me a couple hours.
我待会儿去你家找你
I'll meet you back at your place.
如果你逼我离开的话  就不用来找我了
If you make me leave, don't come over.
你他妈为什么搞得像个娘们儿一样
Why the fuck you acting like a girl, huh?
我厌倦了活在谎言中  你不是吗
I'm sick of living a lie. Aren't you?
我没有对你撒谎
I'm not lying to you.
那对其他人呢
Everyone else?
谁他妈在乎其他人啊
Who gives a shit about everybody else?
就算我对他们撒谎又怎么样
What fucking difference does it make if I lie to them?
因为
'cause--
因为你不自由
Because you're not free.
伊恩  跟你在一起的时候  我就是自由的
Ian, what you and I have makes me free...
这些混蛋们是不会懂的
Not what these assholes know.
瞧瞧伊利诺伊州把谁给放归社会了
Look who the state of Illinois just released back into society.
老爸回家啦
Daddy's home!
搞起来
Come on.
为什么我的手中还没有啤酒呢
Why don't I have a beer in my hand?
给你
Here it is.
在这儿呢  是吧
Right there,huh?
你好啊  宝贝
Hello, honey.
看这老爸一来就吓破胆的小男孩
Look at scared little boy running to daddy.
咬我啊
Eat me.
我传闻中的小孙子在哪里
Where's this grandson of mine I keep hearing about?
他在这儿  老爸
Here he is, pops.
让我看看这个小家伙
Let me look at the little shit.
哎呀  真可爱
Oh, my, my, my.
真是可爱的小东西
He's a cute little fucker.
这是爷爷
That's grandpa.
好了  派对闹起来
All right, let's party!
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
好了  来
Oh, okay, huh? Come on.
好了
All right.
我们给你姐姐发张照片吧
Let's take a picture for your sister, huh?
怎么样
Yeah?
试一下
Let's try.
试一下  好吗
Let's try, huh?
看看
Let's see.
好了  准备好了吗
All right, here we go. Ready?
笑一下
Smile.
还不赖  是吧
That's not bad, huh?
挺不错的
That's pretty good.
好了
All right.
希望你能收到
Hopefully you get this.
监狱里怎么样
Uh, how's the pokey, huh?
有女朋友了吗
You get a girlfriend yet?
可别掉了肥皂
Don't drop the soap.
我们挺好的
Uh, we're good.
再坚持89天  好吗
Only 89 more days, okay?
坚持住  我爱你
Hang in there. I love you.
你有什么要说的吗  说吧
Anything you want to say? Go.
菲奥娜  菲菲菲
Fiona. Fififi.
好
Good.
好了
All right.
太好了
Perfect.
你先自己玩一会好吗
Okay, now you go play for a little bit, okay?
-好  -我去做晚饭
- Okay. - I'll make dinner.
能帮我把自己的外套和帽子脱掉吗
Can you take your jacket and hat off for me too?
好了  真乖  马上回来
All right. Good boy. Be right back.
怎么了
What?
没事
Nothing.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我也是
Me too.
我觉得我们不应该这样
I don't-- I don't think we should.
为什么
Why not?
我们才刚认识
I mean, we just met.
你说的对
You're right.
也许我们应该
Maybe we should, uh--
也许应该等到舞会之后
I don't know-- wait till the dance.
你在邀请我去舞会吗
You're asking me to the dance?
如果你愿意跟我去的话
I don't know. I mean, if you'll go with me.
没问题
Yeah!
没想到吧
Surprise!
西玛
Seema?
看来你已经见过我继弟亨利了
I see you've met my stepbrother, Henry.
继弟
Stepbrother?
你为什么要这样对我
Why would you do this to me?
西玛给了我50块钱
Seema gave me 50 bucks.
-给我遥控器  -我操
- I call dibs on the remote! - Fuck.
-我要看史蒂夫·哈维  -给我  我先来的
- I want to watch Steve Harvey! - I call--I was here first.
-那不算  -才怪
- That doesn't matter. - Yes, it does.
不算  根本没关系
No, it doesn't. That has nothing--
不
Nope.
-你们是谁  -我们是卡尔的朋友
- Well, who the hell are you? - We're friends of Carl.
他在哪儿
Okay, where is he?
那儿吗
There?
玩你自己的去
Go get your own.
给我
Give me it!
下面不会有什么东西会让我掉下去吧
Is there something on the bottom to break my fall?
估计不会
Probably not.
酷
Cool.
把她弄出来  你干什么呢
Yo, get her out of there. What are you doing?
是你爸吗
Is that your dad?
不是
No.
楼下那群熊孩子是怎么回事
Who the fuck are those kids downstairs?
-他们住在货车里  -关我什么事
- They live in a van. - Why is that my problem?
现在是冬天
It's the winter.
让他们走  行吗
Just get rid of them, okay?
我改主意了  他们可以留下
No, on second thought, they can stay.
-太好了  -只能呆到晚饭后
- Cool. - Just till after dinner.
然后就让他们回去
Then they're gone.
好吧
All right.
-给我  -不
- Give it! - No!
这是我的遥控器  玩你自己的去
This is my remote! Get your own!
-不  -给我
- No! - Give it!
玩吧  大声点
Uh, play. Uh, be loud.
想干嘛干嘛
Just do whatever the fuck you want, okay?
好吧
All right!
别用球砸我
Don't hit me with the ball!
是你用球砸我
You with the ball!
好了
Right.
你再敢用球砸我试试
Don't ever hit me with the ball!
欢迎
Welcome.
你好  我是儿童与家庭服务部的
Hello, I'm Wesley Gretsky
韦丝莉·格列茨基
from DCFS.
糟糕  抱歉
Shit, sorry.
是社工  对吧
Uh, the--the social worker, right?
我们正等着您呢
Yeah, we've, uh... We've been expecting you.
我能不能进去检查一下
I'd like to come in, please, do an inspection.
好的  没问题
Right, okay. Yeah.
能不能再约时间来检查呢
Hey, listen, is there any chance in rescheduling, you think??
如果跟你预约安排
Wouldn't be a surprise visit
就不叫随机抽查了  对吧
if we rescheduled, now, would it?
是  是啊
No. No, I guess not.
进来吧
Yeah.
-玩你自己的去  -看看楼上
- Go get your own. - Watch upstairs.
给我
Give it!
请站成两列
Form two lines, please.
当我叫到你名字的时候
All right, when I call your name,
出列  给你们分配铺位
step up and get your bunk assignment.
奥德丽·梅尔尼克
Melnick, Audrey.
32号床
Bed 32.
菲奥娜·加拉格
Gallagher, Fiona.
44号床
Bed 44.
-谢谢  -先别急着谢
- Thank you. - Don't thank me yet.
你还没试过床呢
You ain't tried the bed yet.
马屁拍在马脚上了吧  贱人
Got some brown on your nose, bitch.
詹妮弗·朗菲尔德
Longfield, Jennifer.
35号床
Bed 35.
坦尼莎·罗伯茨  36号床
Roberts, Tanesha. Bed 36.
吃我的屎吧  婊子
You can fucking eat my ass, cunt.
老娘再说一遍
I tell you one more time--
-你他妈离我远点  -贱婊子
- Get the fuck out of my face. - Dirty ass dick.
滚开  快点
Move! Now!
你他妈看什么看
What the fuck are you looking at?
没事
Nothing.
我怎么会在这  妈咪
Why am I here, Mommy?
亲爱的  我说过了
Oh, honey, I told you.
你出事故了  记得吗
You had an accident, remember?
但医生们把你治好了
But the doctors made you all better.
那我们该走了
Well, then we should go.
我们要是不回家做晚餐  爸比会生气的
Daddy's gonna be mad we're not home to make dinner.
不  他会理解的
No, he'll understand.
不好意思  探病时间结束了
Sorry, folks. Visiting hours are over.
好吧
Oh, okay.
晚安  老爸
Night, pops.
明儿一早就来看你
Be back first thing in the morning.
再见  小黛
Good-bye, Deb.
再见  我亲爱性感的汉子
Good-bye, my sweet, sexy man.
妈  别这样
Mom, stop.
大庭广众的
We're in public.
是哦  我忘记是你妈妈了
Oh, that's right. I forgot I'm Mom.
等我们回家的
Wait till we get home.
这些得放好
These need to be stored properly,
要盖上盖子
with caps on them.
这些东西都非常稀释了
Ah, stuff's so diluted, I mean,
里面应该也没剩什么清洁成分了
I doubt there's even any cleaning product left.
把柜子锁上也行
A locked cabinet would also work.
这上面要装一个火警器
Need a fire alarm up there,
-以及二氧化碳探测器  -好
- as well as a CO2 detector. - Okay.
这节楼梯的地板凸出来了
Floorboard is coming up on this step.
下面一节有几根暴露的钉子
Couple of exposed nails on the one below.
孩子们
Hey, uh, guys, yo!
你们能小点声吗
You think you could keep it down?
是你让我们想干嘛就干嘛的
You told us we could do whatever we want.
现在我让你们小点声
Now I'm telling you to keep it down.
这些孩子都哪来的
Who are these children?
邻居家的  我帮忙照顾
Uh, neighborhood kids. I'm babysitting.
监管六名或以上的孩子就算是日托了
Six children or more is considered a day care...
好吧
Okay.
日托就需要执照
For which you will need a license...
好吧
Okay.
我想你应该没有吧
Which I don't imagine you have.
你想得没错
Uh, you--you've imagined correctly.
去弄张执照
Get a license
不然就少看几个孩子
or babysit less kids.
暴露的电线  我马上处理
Uh, exposed wires. Yeah, I'm on it.
-最重要的一个问题  -你问
- Now for the $24,000 question. - Yeah.
这个家的监护人在哪里
Where are the guardians of this household?
弗兰西斯和菲奥娜·加拉格
I have a Francis and Fiona Gallagher,
父亲和大姐
father and sister.
他们在上班
Yeah, they're at work.
-他们让你照顾这儿  -是的
- They put you in charge? - That's correct.
你跟这个家庭是什么关系
What is your relationship to this household?
我跟这个家的关系
My relationship to the household.
我是大哥
I'm the, uh... the eldest brother.
我19岁
I'm--I'm 19.
如果我给那两位监护人打电话
So, if I were to call Mr. and Miss Gallagher,
会发现他们在上班
I'd find them both at work?
是的
Yeah.
阿曼达跟她父母来了
Amanda's here with her parents.
这位是利普
This is Lip.
这两位是我的父母  杰森和雪儿
These are my parents, Jason and Sheryl.
他们是白种人
They're white.
看得出来
I can see that.
幸会
Hi, nice to meet you.
我没提过我是被领养的吧
I guess I never told you I was adopted, huh?
没有
No.
他们从苏比克湾一家妓院买的我...
Well, they bought me from a Subic Bay whorehouse, so...
冲啊  海军
Go, navy.
阿曼达  这是我们的家事
Amanda, that's our private business.
没事
Uh, no, don't worry.
你们正置身我们家的家事中呢
You're right in the middle of our private affairs.
那位是儿童与家庭服务部的韦丝莉
That's, uh, Wesley from the DCFS.
她是来随机拜访的社工
She's a social worker here on a surprise visit.
-也许她是你亲妈  -这位是我弟卡尔
- Maybe she's your real mom. - And that's my brother Carl.
这些是他的朋友们  他们住在小货车里
These are his friends. They live in a van.
谁想吃晚餐啦
So who's ready for dinner?
我
Me!
去吧
Go on!
来吧
Come on.
菲奥娜
Fiona?
菲奥娜  你醒着吗
Fiona, you're awake?
菲奥娜
Fiona?
你是在跟我说话吗
Are you talking to me?
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?
睡觉
Sleeping.
你呢
What are you doing?
不睡觉
Not sleeping.
不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
我们小声点说话  别把莫妮卡吵醒
Let's be quiet so we don't wake up Monica.
莫妮卡
Monica?
对不起  我们昨晚把你和你弟
I'm sorry we left you and your brother
留在了华盛顿公园
in Washington Park last night.
毒贩给了我们一份样品
The dealer gave us a sample.
我忘记你和利普在外面等着了
I forgot you and Lip were waiting outside.
你们等了多久
How many hours was that?
你们可能会冻死的
You could've frozen to death.
我保证以后会成为一个更好的爸爸
I promise I'm gonna be a better dad.
没关系
It's okay.
你生我气了吗
You mad at me?
没有
No.
要我明天带你去克莱尔家
Want me to take you to Claire's tomorrow,
打耳洞吗
get your ears pierced?
好
Okay.
很高兴你在这儿陪我  菲奥娜
I'm glad you're here with me, Fiona.
我也很高兴  爸爸
Me too, Daddy.
然后我就海扁了他们一顿
So then I pummeled their fucking face in good.
这样就能教教那些死基佬
That'll teach the queers
下次别他妈想上米尔科威奇了  是吧
to try to rape a Milkovich in the prison, huh?
说到基佬
Speaking of queers.
你他妈想干嘛
What the hell do you think you're doing?
该让你爸知道
I thought your father should know
他没把你骨子里的基性全揍出来
he didn't beat all the queer out of you.
这次他真会杀了你的
Really gonna kill you this time.
你他妈最好闭嘴
Keep your fucking mouth shut.
能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
你此时此刻的生活水准
You know, your life right here, right now
已经是你今生的巅峰了
is as good as it's ever gonna get.
你得干一整天男人
You got to go get plowed all day, yeah,
但你回到家还有片瓦遮头
but you come home to a roof over your head
能吃上饱饭
and food in your fucking belly.
五年后
Five years from now,
你会变成一个吸毒上瘾
you're gonna be a used-up,
又老又干的鸡
dried-up old whore,
在路边五块钱给男人打次嘴炮
sucking guys off on the sidewalk for five bucks a pop.
换做我是你  我就不会毁了这一切
I wouldn't fuck this up if I were you.
我就想跟你说一声  我要走了
I just wanted to let you know that I'm leaving.
好  回你家见
Okay, I'll see you back at the place.
不  你见不到了
No, don't.
我们玩完了
We're done.
你他妈说什么呢
What the fuck are you talking about?
我对地下情已经没兴趣了
I don't have any interest in being a mistress anymore.
我的天  你什么时候变得这么矫情
Jesus christ. When did you get so dramatic?
因为我意识到你是个娘炮
When I realized what a pussy you are.
你敢再说一遍  我就揍死你
Say it again, I'm gonna kick your fucking ass.
来呀  过来呀  硬汉
Come on. Come on, big guy.
你觉得自己是爷们儿吗
You think you're a tough man, huh?
你不是
You're not.
你是个懦夫
You're a coward.
滚蛋
Fuck you.
你懂个屁
You don't understand.
我当然懂
Oh, I do understand.
我比谁都懂
I understand better than anyone
你怕你老子
That you're afraid of your father.
怕你老婆
You're afraid of your wife.
不敢做你自己
You're afraid to be who you are.
好啊  你走吧
Well, good. Leave.
我他妈才无所谓呢  混蛋
What the hell do I care, bitch?
操
Fuck.
我有话说
Excuse me!
大家听我说两句
Can I get everybody's attention, please?
我要告诉在座的诸位
I just want everybody here to know
我他妈是同性恋
I'm fucking gay.
基爆了
A big old 'mo.
我觉得该把这件事告诉大家
I just thought everybody should know that.
你满意了吗
You happy now?
我要宰了你
I'll fucking kill you!
王八蛋
You son of a bitch!
等这一刻好久了
Been wanting to do this forever.
该死
Oh, shit.
我还是报警吧
I better call the cops.
能把手机递给我吗
Hey, hand me my phone, would you?
外面冷
It's cold out here.
无所谓
I don't care.
我也是
I don't either.
今天学校的事情我听说了
I heard what happened at school today.
听你那个傻逼女友说的吗
What, your stupid girlfriend tell you?
她已经不是我女友了
She's not my girlfriend anymore.
看见她脸书上的照片以后
I broke up with her after I saw
我就和她分手了
the pictures she posted to facebook.
这些照片吗
You mean like these ones?
我觉得照片拍得挺好看的
I think you look pretty.
全校七八年级的人都在笑话我
I'm the laughingstock of the seventh and eighth grade,
九年级的人可能也知道了
maybe even the ninth too.
也有很多人发状态支持你的
Yeah, there are lots of posts that are "Team Debbie."
像这条吗
You mean like this one?
"美胸一对  我显微镜呢"
"Nice titties. Where's my microscope?"
风头会过去的
It'll blow over.
我还以为他喜欢我
I thought he liked me.
他邀我当舞伴
He asked me to the dance.
男生都是...
Boys are...
蠢蛋
jackasses.
他还送我一颗青蛙心脏
He gave me a frog heart.
他什么
He what?
我真是不擅长恋爱
I suck at love.
谁不是呢  我还和西玛交往了呢
Yeah, tell me about it. I dated Seema.
你喜欢她哪一点
What did you like about her?
她看着人不错
She seemed nice.
其实一点也不好
She wasn't.
是啊  狡猾的女人
Yeah, well, girls are sneaky.
她们从来不把真实的自己展现给你
They never really show you their true colors.
我对她也很恶劣
I was mean to her too, though.
没错  但你还小
Yeah, but you're the kid.
她已经是大人了
She's the adult.
应该更懂事
She should've known better.
我不小了
I'm not a kid.
我带你去舞会吧
I'll take you to the dance.
真的吗
Really?
被人看见跟我在一起  你不尴尬吗
You won't be embarrassed to be seen with me?
不  不
No. No.
我会很自豪的
No, I'll be proud.
死基佬
Fucking faggot!
滚出我家
Get out of my house!
你这舔鸡巴的变态
You pole-smoking queer!
去你妈的  不用你担心
Fuck you! Don't worry about it!
打你坐牢那时候起
I've been staying at Ian's
老子就和伊恩一起住了
since you've been in the can, bitch.
猜猜我和他每天都在干嘛  爸爸
Guess what we've been doing, daddy!
我们做爱
We've been fucking!
我是受
And I take it!
他器硬活好
He gives it to me good and hard,
爽死我了
And I fucking like it.
-放开我  -冷静点  特里
- Let me go! - Calm down, Terry.
混蛋
Fuck you!
我给他吹箫
I suck his dick.
也他妈爽
I fucking love it.
把他带走
Get him out of here!
混蛋
Fuck you!
老子要把你的卵蛋撕碎了
I'm gonna cut your balls in little pieces
再塞回你的屁眼里去
and shove them up your ass so far,
你他妈要蛋何用
you grow ball trees, you fuck.
你发什么疯  特里
What is your problem, Terry?
才出来四小时
You been out for four hours,
就和人打起来了
and you're already into a fight?
你违反了假释规定
You're breaking your probation.
混蛋  混蛋
Fuckers! Fuckers!
至于你...
And as for you...
你可以走了
You're free to go.
什么
What?
要是逮捕你
If I arrest you,
我得做很多文书工作
it's gonna be a lot of paperwork.
今晚都别想离开办公室了
Keep me in the office all night.
我还想回家陪老公卡洛斯呢
I'd rather get home to my husband, Carlos.
我和邦尼吃完了
Me and Bonnie are finished.
我们上楼了
We're heading upstairs.
好
All right.
别忘了给你姐姐发电邮
Email your sister, yeah?
利普的姐姐进监狱了
Oh, Lip's sister's in prison.
不会吧
No way.
我们阿姨也在里面
Our auntie's in prison too.
是吗  她犯什么事了
She is? For what?
谋杀  她在死囚牢房
Murder. She's on death row.
你...  你姐姐因为什么进去的
Why--why is your sister in prison?
第一次
Uh, well, the first time
是差点让利亚姆吸食可卡因致死
was for almost killing Liam here with cocaine,
然后...  第二次
And, uh--and then the second time
是违反保释条例
was for breaking probation
跟最初给他可卡因的那家伙鬼混去了
and going out with the guy who gave her cocaine.
天呐  你的生活还真是"多姿多彩"
My, you--you have quite a colorful story.
说的好听是这样
That's a nice way of putting it.
不喜欢你们的晚餐吗
You don't like your dinner?
我们午餐吃得晚
Oh, we had a late lunch.
好的  如果您不介意
Okay, if you don't mind,
那我就把...
I'm just gonna...
打扰一下
Excuse me.
如果您饿了的话
if you're hungry.
味道很一般
It's not very good.
那些孩子都住在货车里吗
So all those kids live in a van?
是的  很显然是
Uh, yeah. Yeah, apparently.
现在你在照顾他们吗
And you're watching them?
是  货车冬天多冷啊
Well, yeah, vans are, uh, cold,
地方又小
you know, crowded.
大多数人都在想怎么摆脱自己的孩子
Most people I see are trying to dump their kids,
而不是收养更多
not collect more.
邻居之间要互相帮忙
You know, neighborhood's got to stick together.
好了  给你
There you go.
看起来  我的下次来访时间是
And it looks like my next surprise visit here
两周后的星期六下午四点
will be in two Saturdays at 4:00 p.m.
晚安
Have a good night.
好的  我来开门
Okay. Uh, I'll get that.
你的成绩出来了
Hey, your grades are up.
是的  我看见了
Oh, yeah, I saw.
英文得了C
"C" in English.
看来我要失去奖学金
I'm gonna lose my scholarship
退学回家了
and have to drop out of school.
那太糟糕了
Oh, that's too bad.
除非你宏观经济学和哲学都考了A
Unless you got an "A" in macro and philosophy
热学考了B
and a "B" in thermo.
真的假的  让我看看
What? Let me see that.
我靠
Holy shit.
太棒了
That's fantastic.
笑一个
Smile.
正点
Cool.
在跟你姐姐介绍我吗
Telling your sister about me?
"我跟我女朋友邦妮在你的床上
"I'm in your bed with my girlfriend, Bonnie.
在监狱老实呆着
Stay in prison.
爱你  卡尔"
Love, Carl."
我不喜欢做爱
I don't like sex.
但我们还是可以亲亲抱抱
But we can still kiss and stuff if you want.
行  我喜欢
Yeah, I like this.
我也是
Me too.
我认为这种环境
This is not the environment
不适合我的女儿
that I want for my daughter.
杰森  出什么事了
Jason, what happened?
有个小孩都快把自己的屎吃下去了
There is a child who almost ate his own feces out there.
可能他晚餐吃少了
Oh, shit, guess he didn't get enough dinner.
我希望你不要再跟阿曼达交往
I'd like you to stop seeing Amanda.
这又不是你说了算的
It's kind of not your choice.
多少
How much?
什么多少
How much what?
杰森  别这样
Jason, don't.
为什么  你希望阿曼达跟他在一起吗
Why, because you want her to be with him?
她是成年人了
She's an adult.
她是由我养活的成年人
Yeah, she's an adult who I'm supporting.
给你多少钱  你才肯跟她分手
How much to stop dating her?
抱歉
Excuse me?
你知道  她并没有爱上你
You know, she's not in love with you.
你知道的  对吧
You do know that, right?
我们还没走到那一步
We're not really at that stage yet.
她只是想用跟你这样的人交往
She's just trying to drive me crazy
来激怒我
by going out with someone like you.
-我这样的人  -是的
- Someone like me? - Yeah.
你看起来  是个不错的孩子
I mean, you seem like a perfectly nice kid,
但阿曼达只是在叛逆期罢了
but Amanda's just rebelling.
谁能怪她呢
Well, don't blame her.
身边有你这么个混蛋
You're kind of a dick.
我不否认
I'm not denying that.
那么  五千块怎么样
How about $5,000, then?
对这个地方来说可不是个小数目
Looks like that would go pretty far in this place.
-杰森  -他是认真的吗
- Jason. - Is he serious?
他要买通我跟他女儿分手吗
He's gonna pay me not to date your daughter?
一万块呢
How about $10,000?
我身上就有现金
I have the cash with me.
随身带着吗  在这样的街区
On you, in this neighborhood?
成交吗
Have we got a deal?
菲奥娜
Hey, Fiona.
你饿了吗
You hungry?
我要去给我俩弄点吃的
I'm gonna go get us something to eat.
老天
Oh, god.
拜托
Ah, jeez!
尿袋
你爸爸刚刚给了我一万块钱
So your father just offered me 10 grand
条件是离开你
to stay away from you.
阿曼达  你知道我们是爱你的
Amanda, you know we love you.
你拿了他的钱吗
Did you take the money?
你觉得呢
Uh, what do you think?
你拿了
That you did.
真的吗
Really?
到底拿了没有
Well, did you?
拿了
Yeah.
那我们这算是玩完了对吧
So we're breaking up, then?
收人钱财替人消灾  不对吗
Well, a deal's a deal, right?
好了  阿曼达  我们走吧
Okay, Amanda, come. We're leaving.
是你说男人要说话算话的
Look, you taught me to be a man of my word.
我才刚觉得真心喜欢上你了
And I was just starting to really like you.
才一万块
10 grand?
我慌了
I panicked.
都跟你说他给我高中的前男友
I told you he gave my ex boyfriend
一万五了
in high school $15,000.
我不确定他身上现金有没有那么多
I didn't know he was gonna have the cash on him.
你应该再坚持一下的
You should've held out.
我还从来没见过那么多钱
I'd never seen that much money before.
基佬  是吗
Gay, huh?
我觉得我的牙好像断了一半
I think I broke half a fucking tooth.
我的肋骨也不太舒服
Yeah, my ribs don't feel so good.
你真的出柜了
So you really came out, huh?
不代表我要开始穿裙子或什么的
Doesn't mean I'm gonna wear a fucking dress or anything.
没人让你穿裙子
Nobody fucking asked you to.
不过你的确有双美腿
Though you do have really nice legs.
你真他妈是个混蛋
You're a fucking dick.
是啊  就那个
Yeah, there.
那个就是你得到的东西
That's what you get.
好了
All right, I'm calling it.
记下死亡时间  9点05分
Mark the time of death, 9:05.
不
No!
菲奥娜
Fiona.